웃긴 일 있어?
What's so funny?
아니, 연기 연습 삼아
가짜로 웃어보는 거야
Nothing. It's an acting exercise.
I'm practicing my fake laugh.
넌 왜 웃는데?
What? What's so funny?
안돼, 안돼, 절대로!
여긴 금연이라네
No, no. There's none of that in here.
봐줘요,
이것만 피우고 말게요
Come on. At least let me
finish this last one.
좋아, 나 한 모금만!
Only if you give me a drag.
그래요
악마의 담배여...
저의 죄를 용서하소서
Oh, dark mother, once again
I suckle at your smoky teat.
그거 잡고 기도나 하세요
Why don't you hold on to that one.
제발 냅둬 줄래?
That's like the least fun game ever.
I'm sick of your smoking,
so I brought something...
더 이상은 못 보겠어
금연하게끔 도와줄게
...that is going to help you quit.
금연 패치도 소용없어
That patch is no good.
It's a hypnosis tape.
이건 최면 테입이야
우리 직장 동료는
이걸 2주간 듣고는 끊었어
A woman at work used it for two weeks
and hasn't smoked since.
- 그게 무슨 뜻이야?
- 별 뜻 없어
What's your problem?
Nothing. It's just that
hypnosis is beyond crap.
최면은 다 허튼 소리야
애틀란틱 시티에서
최면에 걸린 적 있잖아
I watched you get hypnotized
in Atlantic City.
난 최면에 걸리지 않았어
That guy did not hypnotize me, okay?
그래서 셋만 세면, 바지 내리고
엉덩이로 이름을 썼어?
You always pull your pants down
and play "Wipe Out" on your butt.
최면 얘기는 그만 하자
Forget hypnosis.
금연하려면, 잔디밭에서
발가벗고 춤을 추다가
The way to quit smoking is to
dance naked in a field of heather...
땀으로 범벅이 되면
그때 목욕을 해
...and then bathe in the sweat
of six healthy, young men.
아빠가 전화만 하면
땡기는 걸 어쩌냐
Or what my father calls
"Thursday night."
The One With the Hypnosis Tape
받아, 너도
-Here you go.
-I didn't want cinnamon on this.
난 계피 싫어하는데
미안하다
Sorry.
- 안녕
- 이게 누구야?
Oh, my God! Frank!
- 안녕
- 프랭크!
How are you?
잘 지냈어?
What are you doing here?
여긴 웬일이니?
I would've called,
but I lost your number.
전화하려고 했는데
누나 번호를 잃어버렸어
엄마한테 쫓겨나서
집에 갈 수도 없고...
And then my mom locked me out of
the house, so I couldn't find it.
동네 공중전화는
수화기가 잘려나갔고...
Then I tried to find a pay phone,
and the receiver was cut off.
무슨 일이야?
What happened?
Vandalism.
공공 기물파손이지
But also, what happened
between you and your mom?
아니, 엄마랑 무슨 일 있냐구?
엄마랑 싸웠어
We got in a fight. She said that
I was too immature to get married.
엄마는 내가 결혼하기에
어리대
You're getting married?
- 네가 결혼을?
- 응
My little brother's getting married!
우리 막둥이가 결혼한대!
I knew you'd be so cool about this.
Do you wanna meet her?
누나는 좋아할 줄 알았어
한번 만나볼래?
내가?
Do l?
Do you?
만날래?
그럼, 좋지
Yeah, I do.
알았어
트럭 주차시키고 올게
Cool, all right.
She's just parking the truck.
- 우리 약혼녀 데려올게요, 형!
- 그래
I gonna go get my fiancee, man!
I'd have bet good money that he'd be
the first one of us to get married.
우리들 중에, 프랭크가
제일 먼저 결혼할 거라 생각해
- 정말 좋지 않니?
- 응
Isn't it fantastic?
Don't you think he's
a little young to get married?
그런데 결혼하기엔
좀 어리지 않아?
18살이야
Well, he's 18.
그래, 총각파티 때
술도 못 마실 나이지
It'll be illegal for him to drink
at his own bachelor party.
아가씨도 못 부르지
Yeah, or to get a hooker.
넌 그 생각뿐이냐!
Always illegal, Joe.
여기요! 여긴 내 약혼녀
나이트 부인이야
This is my fiancee...
... Mrs. IKnight.
저쪽이 우리 누나예요
That's my sister.
프랭크가 누나 얘길 많이 했는데
상상하곤 많이 다르네요
You know, it's funny.
Frank told me so much about you, but
you're not how I pictured you at all.
Yeah, I'm a big surprise.
상상을 불허하는 얼굴이죠
- 고마워요
- 앉아요
Here, grab a seat.
어떻게 만났니?
So how did you guys meet?
나이트 부인이...
아니 앨리스는, 미안해
I was in Mrs. IKnight's....
I mean, Alice. Sorry.
I always do that.
맨날 이래요
가정학 선생님이었어요
I was in her home-ec class.
- 얘는 최고의 학생이었죠
- 선생님도 최고였어요
He was my best student.
She was my best teacher.
If that doesn't keep kids in school,
what will?
요즘은 학교에서
저렇게 공부하나?
- 아무튼, 이제 결혼하시죠?
- 네
And so now you guys
are gonna be married?
처음엔 동거도 생각했지만...
We talked about
just living together...
...but we want kids right away.
애를 빨리 갖고 싶어서요
맙소사!
Oh, my God!
좋네요!
Great!
애라니...
프랭크, 넌 준비가 돼있니?
IKids. Frank, are you sure
you're ready for that?
How hard can it be?
어렵긴 하겠지
You know, I mean, babies.
Who doesn't want babies? Right?
아기를...
누가 아기를 싫어하겠어?
And besides,
I never had a dad around.
게다가 난 아빠가 없었는데...
이젠 생길 거야
And now I always will,
because it'll be me.
- 내가 아빠잖아
- 맞아
Really, we do realize that there's
an age difference between us.
저는 우리 둘의 나이 차를
많이 느껴요
다행이군요
안 그러신 줄 알았어요
Good. Because you were
acting like you didn't.
But when it comes to love,
what does age matter?
근데 사랑에 있어서는
나이 차를 못 느껴요
You are falling fast asleep.
당신은 깊은 잠에 빠집니다
깊이, 깊이...
Deeper, deeper, deeper.
You are now completely asleep.
이제 당신은 잠들었습니다
You don't need to smoke.
당신은 담배가 필요 없습니다
당신이 담배를 지배합니다
Cigarettes don't control you.
You are a strong, confident woman...
당신은 강하고...
당당한 여성이므로
담배가 필요 없습니다
... who does not need to smoke.
A strong, confident woman.
강하고 당당한 여성!
You know what?
작년에 만난 남자는 오직
리차드와 훌리오 뿐이었어
I realized in the last year I've
only gone out with Richard and Julio.
나 좀 도와줘, 소개라도
시켜달라구
You gotta help me out, set me up.
Get me back in the game.
문제가 많다
Not a problem.
내가 만나는 패션계 남자들은
거의 남자만 좋아해
I work in fashion, and all I meet
are eligible straight men.
Can I get you something else?
더 필요한 거 있어요?
치즈 케익 한 조각하고...
데이트도 줄래요?
Cheesecake and a date,
if you're giving them out.
친구랑 그냥 한 얘기예요
Haven't we covered that topic?
You just said to her
- 내가 듣기로는...
- 나랑 데이트하고 싶어요?
You wanna go out with me...
금발 가발과 큰 가슴,
그리고 음식 때문에요?
... because of my wig, the big boobs,
and I serve you food.
그게 좋았다면
우리 고모랑 데이트하죠
If that were true,
I'd be dating my Aunt Ruth.
사실, 데이트해봤는데
좀 어색했죠
And the two times we went out,
it was plain awkward.
You think she should go out with me,
don't you?
나랑 데이트하라고
말 좀 해줘요
정말 데이트하고 싶어요?
You sure you wanna go out with her?
That ain't a pretty picture
in the morning.
두 사람의 아침 풍경은
흉할 것 같은데요
That wig all in disarray,
and boobs flung over the nightstand.
가발은 헝클어지고...
가슴 패드는 던져져있고...
심각하게 생각해봐요
Think about it.
Oh, I will.
그러죠
나도 알아
프랭크 인생일 뿐이지
No, I know.
I know that this is Frank's life.
욕하고 싶지 않지만
이건 너무해, 말도 안돼!
I don't wanna be judgmental,
but it's sick. It's sick and wrong!
What, is it the age thing?
왜, 나이 때문에?
아니, 나이는 상관없어
I'm fine with the age thing...
그 놈의 키스 때문에
동생이 질식사할까봐!
...until it sticks its tongue
down my brother's throat.
본인이 좋아하잖아
Pheebs, he seems to enjoy it.
아기 똥 기저귀 갈아주면서
진땀 빼면서도 좋아할까?
You think he'll enjoy it when he's
up to his elbows in diapers...
...of all the babies
they have to have right away?
프랭크에게 좋지 않고
아기에게도 좋지 않아
This is not fair to Frank,
and it's not fair to the babies.
You know what?
It's not good home economics.
가정학적으로도 안 좋아
Have you told him how you feel?
- 두 사람에게 네 기분을 말했어?
- 응
Yes. Not out loud.
조심스럽게
지금 말하지 않으면
걔는 결혼해
If you don't tell him, soon he'll be
married, then you'll hate yourself.
그럼 넌 자신을 미워하게 돼
하지만 내가 반대하면
날 미워할 거야
Yeah, but if I do tell him,
then he's gonna hate myself.
엄마랑도 싸웠다잖아
난 못해
Look at him and his mom.
I can't.
너희들이 잘 달래 봐
But you guys can.
You talk him out of it.
싫어, 싫어, 싫어
Come on, you guys.
부탁이야
너희들이 손해볼 건 없지만
난 많은 걸 잃게돼
You have nothing to lose.
I have everything to lose.
Do you want me to lose everything?
Everything?
동생이랑 원수지길 바래?
그래?
아니
Okay, I'm gonna go get Frank.
프랭크 데려올게
We're walking down the street,
and I turn to you and say:
우리 길에서 만났을 때
내가 "우리 누드쇼 보러갈래?"
했던 거 기억나지?
"Let's go hang out at
Totally Nude Nudes." Remember?
And then you say, "Let's just
hang out at your place."
근데 네가
그냥 집에나 가자 했지?
Well, that was a nice move, dumb ass.
아주 좋은 변화야
I think you should
go out with this guy.
그 남자랑 데이트해
도움이 안 될 남자야
He doesn't do anything for me.
토요일 밤에
'텍사스 레인저'봤지?
Last Saturday night, what happened
on Walker, Texas Ranger?
주인공이 수십 명의 애들을
보호하면서...
Walker was looking for
this big busload of kids.
All right, I get your point.
- 무슨 말인지 알겠다
- 그래
- 안녕
- 어서 와
I forgot the combination to this
about a year ago.
이 가방이랑 어울리는 게
뭔지도 모르면서...
I just carry it around.
갖고 다닌다
You got any Chap Stick?
- 입술 연고 있어?
- 응
금연 테입은 어땠어?
How are those tapes working out?
- 정말 효과 좋더라
- 그래?
Good. I haven't smoked yet today.
오늘 담배도 안 피우고
기분도 좋고...
I feel great and confident.
That is a stunning blouse.
자신감이 생겼어
그 옷 너무 예쁘다
Thank you.
고마워
- 여깄어
- 고마워
-Here you go.
-Thanks.
피트에게 기회를 줘봐
Let's give Pete a chance.
He was funny. He seems really nice.
유머 감각도 있고
착할 거 같아
That check thing was adorable.
- 수표 장난도 귀엽잖아
- 수표 장난?
What check thing?
As a joke, this customer who has a
crush on me, gave me a $20,000 tip.
나한테 반했다는 어떤 남자가
팁으로 가짜 2만 달러를 줬어
수표에 전화번호도 적어줬어
His number's on the check.
He did it so I'd call.
Pete Becker. Pete
피트 베이커, 피트...
Is this him?
이 사람이야?
That's Bill Clinton.
그건 빌 클린턴이지
포옹하고 있는 사람
Who's he hugging?
Oh, my God. That's Pete.
Why is Bill hugging Pete?
세상에! 피트네!
클린턴하고 뭔 사이야?
This guy invented Moss 865.
이 남자가 개발한 모스8605
프로그램을 전 세계가 쓰고 있어
Every office in the world
uses that program.
- 우리도 쓰는데!
- 바로 그거야
-We use it!
-There you go!
모니카가 백만장자랑
데이트하겠다
Monica's gonna go out
with a millionaire.
I'm not gonna go out with him.
이 남자랑 데이트 안 해
그럼 이 수표가 장난이 아니었네
정말 신난다
I can't believe this is a real
$20,000 check. This is so exciting.
Or incredibly offensive.
날 얕본 걸 수도 있어
Yeah, sure. That too.
그럴 수도 있지
What?
왜?
요컨대, 서둘지 말라는 거야
All we're saying is,
don't rush into anything.
그래, 생각해 봐
Come on, think about it.
You're 18. She's 44.
넌 18살이고
약혼녀는 44살이야
When you're 36, she's gonna be 88.
네가 36살이 되면
아내가 88살이 된다구
You don't think I know that?
그런 것도 모를 거 같아요?
요점은...
The point is...
세상엔 네가 접해보지
않은 여자가 많아
...there's a lot of women
you haven't had sex with yet.
그 말이 맞아
He's right. He's right.
This is your time.
넌 지금 한창 때야
You're young. You're weird.
Chicks dig that.
젊고 미래가 있지
여자들은 그걸 좋아해
정말 좋아하는 한 사람과
사랑을 나누는 게 낫지 않아요?
Isn't sex better when it's with
one person that you really care about?
Yeah, in a poem, maybe.
그게 시란 거야
No, the man's right.
That's what I had with Rachel.
그런 건 없어
나도 레이첼과 겪었지
Not anymore?
- 지금은 안 만나요?
- 안 만나...
No. I slept with someone else.
딴 여자랑 잤거든
거 봐요
그래서 나아진 게 있어요?
So wait. So how did that
make things better?
It didn't.
없지
형이 레이첼 누나를 사랑하듯
나도 앨리스를 사랑해요
What you used to have with Rachel
is what I got with Alice.
Now, what is that like?
그게 어떤 건데?
It's so cool, man.
아주 죽이죠!
함께 있는 게 훨씬 좋죠
없을 때보다는...
It's because being with her is so
much better than not being with her.
-Why can't I find that?
-I had it and I blew it.
난 왜 그런 걸 모르지?
- 사랑을 망친 놈한테 묻냐?
- 사랑하고 싶어
Well, I want it!
You can have it.
형도 할 거예요
난 못할 거야
나한테 문제가 있나봐
Maybe there's something wrong with me.
아냐
No, it's out there, man.
I've seen it! I got it!
힘을 내요!
내가 하면 형도 가능해요
-Then, you hold on to it!
-All right, man!
그 여자 꽉 잡아라
- 그래야죠, 형!
- 좋았어, 축하해, 임마
All right! Congratulations,
you lucky bastard!
You're Frank's best man?
프랭크 들러리를 선다구?
I couldn't help it.
Their love is so pure.
어쩔 수 없었어
그들의 사랑은 순수해
What about you, huh?
넌 어떤데?
I'm the ring bearer.
반지 전달해 줄거야
어서 오세요
와 주셔서 감사해요
I'm so glad you could come.
I've got a real home-ec emergency.
가사에 문제가 생겨서요
Oh, my God. Who died on this?
- 누가 여기서 죽었나요?
- 심하죠?
겨자 님이 죽었죠
It's a real "mustard-tastrophe."
Can you help?
- 도와주시겠어요?
- 물론이죠
Absolutely. First, we'll start
with a little club soda and salt.
우선, 소다수와 소금으로 빼보고
안 되면 다른 걸로...
-Then if that doesn't work
-Forget it. It's ruined.
- 됐어요, 그냥 버리죠
- 아뇨, 그러지 말아요
Never say that. If you can't
get it out, cut around the stain...
남은 얼룩을 오려내고
레이스로 장식하면
...add a little lace,
you make a stylish throw.
멋진 스카프가 될 거예요
제 동생과 결혼 안 하시면
더 멋질 것 같은데요
Or instead, maybe you could just
not marry my brother, Frank?
좀 더 작게 만들 순 없나요?
Can we make it smaller?
Make it fit on the head of a pin?
핀의 머리처럼 만들 수 있죠?
그 정도로 작아야 돼요
I love when we make things
fit on the head of a pin.
- 알겠습니다
- 그러죠
You have Monica Geller here.
모니카 겔러 양이
오셨습니다
들여보내세요
Absolutely. Yeah, send her in.
안녕하세요?
What the hell is this?
대체 이게 뭐죠?
Hang on for a sec.
I'll talk to you in the morning?
잠깐만요
- 내일 다시 하죠
- 그러죠
You got it.
I'm sorry. What?
뭐라고 하셨죠?
이게 무슨 뜻이냐구요?
What's this supposed to mean?
Well, you know,
I never know how much to tip.
팁을 얼마나 줘야할지
몰라서요
You double the tax.
Not double the tax of Romania.
세금의 두 배잖아요
이건 어느 나라 계산법이죠?
나를 돈으로 산다는 거예요?
데이트 신청을 돈으로 해요?
Are you buying me? Is this how
you get girls to go out with you?
저 좀... 꺼주세요
I'm still here.
You're taking this wrong.
If I didn't leave you that tip...
무슨 오해가 있나본데...
내가 그 팁을 주지 않았으면
당신이 여기 올 일도 없고
...you wouldn't have come,
we wouldn't have this argument...
이런 말싸움도 없었겠죠
우리 사이에 이런 열기도 없구요
...and there wouldn't be
this heat between us.
뭐요?
You gotta admit that our relationship
is hitting a new level now.
이제 우리가 새로운 국면에
접어들었다는 걸 인정해요
You were the chef
and I was the customer.
전엔 요리사와 손님의
관계였지만
But now we're this couple that fights.
이젠 사랑싸움 같은 것도
하잖아요
과장하지 마세요
You're a loon.
Look, forget the check, okay?
I like you.
수표는 잊어버립시다
난 당신이 좋아요
당신이 맘에 든다구요
I think you're great.
어때요?
Come on, what do you say?
- 모르겠어요
- 왜요?
I don't know.
Why not?
I don't wanna encourage
this behavior.
당신의 술책에
넘어가기 싫어서요
One meal.
That's all I'm asking for. Please?
딱 한 번만요
제발 부탁이에요
We go out, we eat.
식사 한 번 합시다
If you don't have a good time,
I'll give you 10 grand, we're even.
그 시간이 재미없으면
만 달러 줄게요, 공평하죠?
- 왔어?
- 뭐야? 너!
그거 내려놔, 나야
Wait, no. Just put the mail down.
It's me.
그래, 미안해
왜 그러고 있니?
Sorry. Why were you
just all in the dark?
누나 빨래 냄새가 좋아서
둘둘 말고 있었어
Your laundry smelled so good
that I thought I'd curl up in it.
- 일은 잘 돼?
- 응
-ls that all right?
-Yeah, sure.
넌 오늘 어땠니?
So how was your day?
It's just probably the worst one
since I've been alive.
내 평생 이렇게 끔찍한
날은 없었어
무슨 일인데?
What happened?
앨리스가... 헤어지재
Alice....
She called it off.
어머나!
이유가 뭐래?
Did she say why?
모르겠어
그냥 내가 너무 어리대
No. Just that I was too young.
I don't see how I could
suddenly be too young...
어쩌다 갑자기 내 나이가
생각났는지 몰라
... because I'm older than I was
when we first got together.
우리가 처음 만났을 때보다
나이는 더 먹었는데
그래, 안 됐다
난... 잘 모르지만...
I don't know. But you know what?
Maybe it's just all for the best.
이제 앞날만 생각해
이제 나의 앞날은
고통만 있을 거야
Well, yeah, if the best is
like unbelievable pain.
막내야
Oh, sweetie.
You know, I was just finally happy.
정말 행복했었어
For the first time in my life...
내가 태어난 이후
...after my dad left me...
아빠가 가출한 후...
...and then getting arrested
for stealing those birds...
새를 훔쳐서 체포된 후...
폐에 펑크가 난 후...
...and then the whole
punctured-lung thing.
It's still really hard to take
deep breaths in cold weather...
찬바람이 불면
아직도 숨쉬기가 힘든데...
...but with Alice,
all that stuff kind of went away.
앨리스 때문에 모든 게
사라졌다구
And now it's gone,
and I don't know why.
왜 가버렸을까?
이유를 모르겠어
Well, I can tell you why.
It's because of me.
이유를 말해줄게
나 때문이야
널 사랑하기 때문에
그랬어, 괜찮지?
But you know what? I only did it
because I love you, okay?
What?
뭐?
앨리스한테 두 사람이
인연이 아니라고 말했거든
I kind of had a little chat
with Alice...
...and I sort of made her see
why you two shouldn't be together.
너도 곧 알게 될 거야
누나가 장담해
And you'll see it too, one day.
You really, really will.
Wait a minute.
This is because of you?
잠깐...
누나 때문이라구?
- 있잖아...
- 잠깐, 누나...
My mother didn't want us
to be together...
엄마가 날 기둥에
묶어놨던 것에 비하면
...but the worst thing she did
was tie me to the porch.
반대쯤은 아무 것도
아니라고 생각했어
하지만...
여기 온 건, 날 이해할 거라
생각했기 때문이야
I came to you because
I thought you'd understand.
안돼! 누나...
문을 박차고 나가고 싶어
I would storm out of here...
돈과 갈 데만 있으면!
...if I had some money
or a place to go.
Oh, my God! The millionaire's here!
어머!
백만장자가 오셨어
어머나!
Oh, my God!
I'm just gonna have dinner with him.
그냥 저녁 한 끼 먹는 거야
그래, 저녁 한 끼 먹는다고
뭐가 어떻게 되겠니?
Okay, just because he buys you dinner
does not mean you owe him anything.
I know.
나도 알아
Okay, then get the lobster.
가재 먹어라
- 오셨군요
- 안녕하세요
How much cash you got
in your pocket now?
지금 주머니에
돈이 얼마나 있죠?
저렇게 난리니
어서 가시죠
And that's why I'm not
inviting you in for a drink.
다녀올게
Why not? Hey, come in for drink.
- 또 봐요
- 잠깐 들어왔다 가세요
뭐 사주실 거예요?
-Where do you wanna go?
-You like pizza?
- 피자 어때요?
- 그거 좋죠
-That sounds great.
-I know a great little place.
잘하는 곳을 알아요
달을 보는 당신의 눈은
둥그런 피자 같아요
사랑스러워라!
You're not paying for the pizza.
- 피자 값은 내가 내요
- 그러면 안 되죠
Come on, it's only fair.
You paid for the flight.
비행기 표는
당신이 샀잖아요
'리라'로 얼마죠?
Is that enough lira?
I'd throw another 1000 on that.
거기에 천 리라 더 놔요
이게 얼만데요?
-How much is that?
-That's about 60 cents.
60센트요
Every night!
매일 밤 이러냐!
당신이 담배를 지배합니다
You don't need to smoke.
Cigarettes don't control you.
You are a strong, confident woman...
당신은 강하고...
당당한 여성이므로
담배가 필요 없습니다
... who does not need to smoke.
A strong, confident woman...
강하고 당당한 여성은
담배를 피우지 않습니다
... who does not need to smoke.
나도 할 수 있어
안녕, 프랭크
Look, I know that you think I did
this totally evil thing.
내가 네 인생에
악역을 했다는 거 알아
But I so didn't.
하지만 그것만은 아냐
Someone's here who can explain this
better than I can.
내가 설명하기보다는
이분이 하시는 게 좋겠다
안녕, 프랭크
안녕...
나이트 부인
Hi, Mrs. IKnight.
Phoebe's right, Frank.
누나 말이 맞아
It's hard to hear, but it would've
been wrong to go through with it.
그냥 밀고 나갈 수 있는
문제가 아닌 거 같아
내가 이기적이었어
I was being selfish.
Even though we want
the same things right now...
우리가 지금은 같은 것을
원하고 있지만, 미래는 모르잖아
...in the future, we may not.
이거 맞죠?
-ls that what it is?
-Yes, but not just that.
- 네, 그것뿐...
- 그것뿐이 아냐
Not just that.
Even though we love each other
as much as we do...
우리 서로를 많이
사랑하고 있지
... nonetheless....
그렇지만...
- 그렇지만...
Nonetheless.
You're too young...
넌 너무 어려서...
네가 뭘 원하는지 몰라
...to really know what you want.
그렇지
That's right, exactly.
That's a goodbye kiss.
That's good.
작별의 키스 정도는 해야지
잘 가요
Bye-bye.
The important thing is,
is that you see what I'm saying.
중요한 건...
내 말 듣니?
이건 정말로 안돼
This is clearly wrong.
I've decided I'm gonna
let this happen.
결혼을 허락하기로 했어
내 가방 좀 줄래?
Can I just get my purse?
그래, 알았다
Okay, all right, good.
당신이 담배를 지배합니다
당신은 강하고...
Cigarettes don't control you.
You are a strong, confident woman...
당당한 여성이므로
담배가 필요 없습니다
... who does not need to smoke.
조이는 가장 친한 친구다
Joey's your best friend.
You wanna make him
a cheese sandwich every day.
넌 매일 그를 위해
치즈 샌드위치를 만든다
그리고... 아주 비싼
바지를 사준다
And you also wanna buy him
hundreds of dollars worth of pants.